Next up, the weather.
It sure is cold today. It's snowing everywhere!
Today's Weather
Moto.
Motoko, aren't you going
to study with your friends?
Have you prepared for the cold weather?
Not until later.
Oh, okay.
Someone called yesterday.
Huh?
On the phone.
It was a guy.
He said his name was Kitahara.
He asked for "Iura-san."
But obviously, we're all Iuras.
I... see...
Why didn't you give the phone to me?
I hung up.
You idiot!
Jeez. Pipe down, pipe down.
Why'd you hang up on him?!
Are you stupid?!
You're supposed to pass the phone!
What is wrong with you?!
Well, you were in the bath.
And you went to bed early.
So, you like this Kitahara guy?
You don't even know him!
And that's none of your business!
He'd better not be a womanizer.
G
R
Don't bring him home when I'm not here.
I wouldn't!
K-K-Kitahara-kun has someone he likes.
And everyone knows it....
Fidget
They walk home from school together.
Shake
But the girl he likes
a-already has a boyfriend!
Shake
So Kitahara-kun could...
You done?
Ugh... Yeah, I'm done.
I wonder why Kitahara-kun called.
Oh, he said to call off today's
study session if it snows.
Why didn't you just tell me that, idiot?!
Katagiri High School
Please, no more English writing questions...
Hori, I can't take any more...
You'll both manage somehow.
How can you say that?
Did you take the English essay test, too?
Yup, yup.
We were talking about
getting something to eat. You in?
Heck yeah! You know I am!
Checking for new messages
New Message
From: Motoko
You're coming home late, right?
My friend is coming over,
so things might get a little loud.
Take your time
You're coming home late, right?
My friend is coming over,
so things might get a little loud.
Take your time.
Iura
The tea is all set. Sweets, too.
Now I just need to wait.
Iura-san, are you doing
anything after class?
N-No.
I heard we're applying to the same
high school. Care to study together?
It's supposed to be a great way to learn.
Yeah, sure!
Okay, I'll drop my stuff off at home
and head over to your place.
This is just a study session!
What would I think it's anything else?!
He's here!
K-Kitahara-kun, come on in...
Kitahara?!
Wh-What in the world?
You said you'd be be home late.
I never said anything like that.
And I never heard anything
about Kitahara coming over.
Grandpa! Lemme borrow your replica sword!
Stop it!
Huh? My replica sword?
No, we don't need it!
He's just coming over to study!
So, what time's he coming? Pretty soon?
R-Right after he drops off
some stuff at his house.
Hmm...
Study in the living room.
There's no telling what middle
schoolers will try these days.
Maybe I should call the police in advance.
We don't live in the slums!
Jeez! Why don't you get a girlfriend already?
I can't stand you!
You always come straight home!
Believe me, I'd love a girlfriend.
Friends
a-flirting
Hee
hee
Heh
heh
The lovebirds I see every day
make it even worse.
Anyway, should I bring you some tea?
Don't do anything! Stay out!
Maybe she's not home.
Iura-san?
You'd better stay out!
If you come into the living room,
I'm running away from home!
Stay in your room!
If you're not getting up to anything,
what's it matter if I'm there or not?
You disappoint me!
What kind of brother
points a sword at his younger sister?!
Then you put yours down!
It's dangerous, you hear me?!
Excuse me...
Hello...
So you're Kitahara.
Hey!
Are you her older brother?
Correct.
Come in.
Would you like some tea? It's all we have.
Hey!
I'm sorry, Kitahara-kun.
He's just in a bit of a mood.
He's so cool!
Kitahara-kun?
Kitahara-kun!
Huh?
Oh, what is it, Iura-san?
Our tea is rather bitter.
Just the way I like it!
What a jerk of a brother!
Kitahara-kun, you're back.
Care for tea? It's all we have.
I love tea.
It's even more bitter than before.
I'm up to the challenge.
Okay, I'll go make some.
S-Sorry, he's in a mood.
Don't apologize. I'm the one imposing.
How much older is he than you?
Three years. He's a third
year in high school.
I see.
Here's your tea.
Can you not be so rough about it?!
Th-Thank you.
Hold it!
Why are you getting comfortable?
Get out, idiot!
I-It's okay, Iura-san.
Am I intruding?
Of course not!
There you have it, Little Sister.
He's just being polite!
No, he's not. Right, Kitahara?
You don't know him at all!
I'm really sorry, Kitahara-kun.
He's usually not this obnoxious...
Oh. Sorry, I wasn't listening.
Not closely, I mean...
Okay.
And stay out!
What, really?
That's the living room, y'know?
I don't understand Kitahara-kun...
Neither do I.
I think I'm even more lost than you are.
H-How can you say that when
you caused all of this?!
Don't you realize it's all your fault?!
Huh?
How's it my fault, seaweed head?
You're the seaweed head, you marimo!
M-Marimo?!
Give back the old Kitahara-kun...
U-Uh... Sorry?
So you're saying you
don't like Kitahara anymore?
I didn't say that.
But lately, when Kitahara-kun
starts talking to me,
I get the feeling it's
not me he's interested in.
M-Motoko...
H-H-He might be talking to me
because I remind him of you.
Has Kitahara really
strayed so far in your mind?
It wouldn't be so bad if I were cuter,
Get it from their mom
but I look too much like you to be cute!
That's going too far! Apologize to Mom!
And you don't need to worry!
People at school are always
saying how cute I am!
You liar!
That's why you haven't found
even a single girlfriend!
Why would I want multiple?!
Student Council
No, not cute at all.
What would you say if a guy walked up
and asked you if he was cute?
Did you hit your head?
No, I'm fine.
Really?
It's just that...
Motoko says it's my fault she's not cute.
Hey, Motoko-chan's plenty cute.
Thank you, Hori-san! I feel much better!
I wasn't saying it to be nice.
Why not try longer hair?
What? Me?
Your sister, obviously.
It might give a different impression.
Her hair gets unruly,
so she won't grow it out.
I think her short hair is cute, though.
Oh, are you talking about me?
Or perhaps me?
What's with that confident grin?
I was talking about a girl with short hair.
Well, I guess it's a sensitive subject.
I mean, she looks like Iura,
but Motoko-chan's cuter.
Huh? What's wrong with me?!
We're not talking about you.
Well, that's how adolescence goes.
And after adolescence comes estrus.
Are you suggesting my sister's a dog?
Humans don't have estrous cycles. Trust me.
I got a high score on the health exam.
I see!
If we did, maybe we wouldn't have
that declining birth rate problem.
I feel like this is a stupid conversation.
I'm still in my adolescence!
People who're in adolescence
don't go around insisting they are!
Then I guess estrus is next for you.
Fine by me!
Maybe adolescence is why Motoko's
been saying such weird things lately...
Like what?
That I should hurry up and
hook up with Sengoku-san.
Every time you or Miyamura message me,
she asks if it's from a girl.
Well, maybe it's because
you call him Sengoku-san!
She's just joshing you.
Maybe.
I think Ayasaki-san's more attractive
than Sengoku-san, though.
Well, you probably would.
Say, when Motoko-chan was at our place,
she told us about the person she likes.
Maybe she's...
projecting her feelings onto you?
So, the thing is...
The person Moto likes seems to like me.
S-So your sister likes girls?
No.
S-So it's something like this?
Seems rather hard to believe.
Super simple chart
Iura-kun
A-kun (anon)
Motoko-chan
Yeah, that's about the size of it.
Though it is rather hard to believe.
I feel sorry for Motoko-chan.
What about me?
Stolen by her brother?
She must be a soulless husk.
Don't make it sound like she's dead!
And I didn't steal anything!
What do you mean?
You totally swiped him.
It's not like that! I want nothing
to do with this relationship!
I like girls!
Yelling that will only get you into
a different kind of trouble, Shu.
What about Sengoku?
How do you feel about him?
Why are you pushing
Sengoku-san on me, too?
I like Sengoku-san, obviously!
Huh?
Oh, Sengoku-san!
So, Iura likes girls and Sengoku?
This is too much for me!
It's so complicated!
Stop! Don't make things any more confusing!
I'm sorry.
Not you too, Sengoku-san.
You'll hurt my feelings.
Just go get a girlfriend, man.
What am I supposed to do? Make one?
Out of clay, maybe? Will she love me?
My girlfriend
Don't you have someone you're interested in?
Maybe someone in your class?
No, not really...
He seems just like a high schooler.
Um, what's going on?
No idea.
Aren't you going to school today?
Just so you know,
I tried to wake you up before.
Really?
What did I do?
You said, "I know" and went
back under the covers.
What's there to know?!
Oh, do you want some breakfast?
Don't suggest things that will
definitely make me late!
Mom says you need to eat
at least a slice of toast.
I'll take it to go. You should get going, too.
Okay.
I'm off!
It's my first time seeing someone actually
run to school with toast in their mouth.
Th-The toast is drying out my mouth.
I can't eat and run at the same time.
I'll switch to walking...
I'm gonna be late!
SLAM
I was running with toast in
my mouth and ran into a boy!
What if he's a handsome transfer student?!
Yoshikawa-san. Yoshikawa-san, are you okay?
It's me, Iura.
Oh, it's you. Good morning.
Good morning.
Did you sleep in, too?
Yeah, after staying up too long.
We'll be late even if we run.
I'm late! I'm late!
Huh? Why are you walking so leisurely?
What about you, eating an onigiri?
Hate to break it to you,
but we're all gonna be late.
Aw, man.
What's in that?
Just salt.
I'm late! I'm late!
What are you guys doing? We need to hurry!
Tea
You stopped by a convenience store?!
What's in that?
It's a meat bun.
Why does everybody yell about being late?
Who knows?
There's no morning assembly today, right?
Nope.
Let's just walk, then.
Katagiri High School
Oh? You're all here early.
Good morning.
Huh?!
I can't believe it!
You're late, Sengoku?! That never happens!
Huh?
Third-years only have class
in the afternoon today.
I'm here early for a
student council meeting.
Huh?
I-I think I remember hearing
that in homeroom yesterday.
If I'd only known, I could have
put jam on my toast!
What's gotten into you four?
If I'd only known, I could have
put something in my onigiri!
Right, Sengoku?
Like shiso leaves or something!
Huh? Sh-Sh-Shiso?
Are those middle schoolers?
S-So you all showed up to
school early? That's so dumb!
I'm just glad it wasn't just me.
Our teacher made a point of saying that
prospective students were coming today.
Oh, so that's why there were
middle schoolers wandering around.
Yep, that's right.
Where are Miyamura and Yuki?
They went to buy something to drink.
Now, why are you here early, Hori?
Oh, that's because...
Kyon-Kyon!
Ready to hit the school store?
You bet I am.
We can buy whatever we want!
Squee
I get it. There won't be
any lines in the cafeteria.
Wanna go get lunch?
Sure!
There's more middle schoolers.
I wonder if there are lots of 'em.
I dunno. I can't get over
how young they look.
Say, is your sister coming?
Not a chance. She hates being in groups.
If she is here, she'd be on her own—
Um, I think we're somewhere around here.
Kitahara!
What's wrong, Shu?!
Get moving, body!
Is something bothering you?
Um, excuse me.
Huh?
We seem to be lost.
Where do you want to go?
We're supposed to meet up here,
at the edge of the field.
Ah, you can get there faster
from the side entrance.
Follow this hall, go down the stairs
to the right, and you'll end up outside.
Thank you.
Hey, Shu!
Don't call my name! Why would you do that?!
Doesn't know
Iura's
full name
What's with him?
Anyway, thank you again.
Sure. Take care now.
He's finally leaving.
What are you doing?
C'mon, Iura-kun, let's go!
Once lunch break starts, it'll get crowded!
Ayasaki-san!
Iura-kun, c'mon!
What's wrong, Kitahara?
Why is a girl calling my name
now of all times?
Hey! Earth to Iura-kun!
But if I move, Kitahara will see me!
Earth to Iura-kun!
I'm sorry, Ayasaki-san! Go on without me!
Iura-kun?
Iura, hurry up.
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Pressure
Huh?
You're...
Senpai?
"Senpai," huh?
If he'd called me anything else,
I would've pretended not to know him!
Senpai, I...
It's hard to pretend I don't know
him when he calls me that...
Scram already!
H-Hey, you're supposed to be outside!
Get going!
Ow!
WHACK
Why are you bullying him, Iura?!
Don't go around scaring middle schoolers!
They're way more scared of you, Yasuda.
Do you know Iura?
Do you go to Iura's middle school?
Um, does he have a girlfriend?
S-Stifled giggles and sympathy...
What do we say? That he does?
Let's respect his wishes.
I feel even more pathetic!
That's enough. You're leaving!
Care to join us at the school store?
No!
We have to go back to school for lunch.
Oh.
Phew.
Is that a relief?
You're freaking me out today. Leave already.
Senpai—
Okay, okay, you guys quit
lollygagging and get going.
I'll take you where you
need to go, so follow me.
Y-Yes, sir.
Yasuda, you should be nice to us, too.
Why's that? You're never nice to me.
Aw...
Yasuda, thank you.
The first time Iura's
ever thanked Yasuda
Peach Tea
Aw!
I would have liked to see that!
Me too, me too!
Huh? Why? It wasn't funny at all.
Sure it was.
You were acting the part of his senpai!
Wh-What's wrong with that?
Nothing, that's what!
But you don't usually react
to people so negatively.
Are you on bad terms?
That boy seemed comfortable around him.
He's in the same class as my sister.
He just happened to be here today.
What? They you you should try
to get along with him!
Well, y'know...
What? Why are you being so wishy-washy?
Is there something else about him—
Was it him? Is he the one?
He is, isn't he?!
Aw, I didn't get to see him!
Me neither!
Shu, is that true? For real?
Who is this middle schooler?
No idea.
Next time
page.6 Sleepover